

ABOUT ME

Experienced software developer with 10 years in the industry and dedicated full stack developer with 2 years in React, Redux, Node, Express, Oracle and MongoDB.

I've worked in different environments, from start-ups to big corporate firms.

Apart from my professional career I supported a Silicon Valley based start-up as a freelancer using Angular, Firebase and Google Cloud.

I am a self-motivated and self-taught professional who likes to solve problems.

I DJ and produce music as a hobby in my spare time.

SKILLS

Front End: ReactJS, Angular+2, Ionic, MaterialUI, SemanticUI, HTML5, CSS3, JSON, RESTful API

Back End: Node, Express, SQL, PL/SQL, Google Cloud, **Firebase**

Databases: Oracle, MongoDB

Testing: Testinium **SCM:** GitHub, GitLab

OS: Windows, macOS, Linux

SDLC: Agile, Scrum

CERTIFICATES

- * Google Cloud Platform Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure
- * Google Elastic Cloud Infrastructure: Foundation, Containers and Services, Core Services
- * Oracle E-Business Suite Supply Chain Management Support Specialist
- * Oracle E-Business Suite R12.1 Supply Chain Management PreSales

EDUCATION

Istanbul Commerce University (2003 - 2007) Bachelor Of Computer Engineering

CAGATAY UCER

www.cagatayucer.com www.linkedin.com/in/cagatayucer github.com/cucer

Experience

TURKISH ECONOMY BANK (BNP JV) (2016 – Present)

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Developed a full-stack web application that allows users to track their progress on our Agile environment. The application also tracks teams, themes, releases, sprints and then provides a summary of progress. Our technology includes many popular solutions such as React, Redux, NodeJs, ExpressJs, OracleDB, MongoDB and many more.

Used Agile and Scrum methodoligies for better software quality and worked closely with UX designer, testers, and clients to identify features the software needs.

Built stored packages, procedures and functions in Oracle DB using PL/SQL for accounting projects.

I also created many pages and solutions for accounting team using Oracle Applications.

EXPERTEAM CONSULTANCY (2014 – 2016)

SENIOR CONSULTANT DEVELOPER

Turkcell Project

Worked closely with Analysts and Customers to develop new and advance existing tools, involving both backend processing engines and UI components.

JOHNSON CONTROLS (2013 – 2014)

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Worked closely with EU clients to develop new and advance existing tools. Designed and implemented customized Forms using Oracle Forms. Designed/modified/implemented stored procedures, triggers in Oracle

AKTEK (2011 – 2013)

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Worked on Oracle E-Business Suite AP, AR, GL, PO and INV modules to provide support to the clients and solving the issues.

Designed and implemented customized Forms using Oracle Forms. Designed/modified/implemented stored procedures, triggers in Oracle using PL/SQL. Prepared the technical specifications and user's manual.

INNOVA (2010 – 2011)

ORACLE CONSULTANT DEVELOPER

Worked on Oracle E-Business Suite HR, PO and INV modules to provide support to the clients and solving the issues.

Coded in PL/SQL Packages, Procedures, Functions, and Views. Developed reports using Oracle Reports and OracleBI Discoverer Plus

Designed and modified customized Forms using Oracle Forms.

APPSCON (2010 – 2010)

ORACLE CONSULTANT DEVELOPER

Worked on Oracle E-Business Suite HR, PO and INV modules to provide support to the clients and solving the issues.

Coded in PL/SQL Packages, Procedures, Functions, and Views. Developed reports using Oracle Reports and OracleBI Discoverer Plus Designed and modified customized Forms using Oracle Forms.